# Hanna Chumakova | Product Designer

347.703.8841 | anna.chumakova95@gmail.com

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I'm a researcher by training, leveraging skills in QA analytics and determined to innovate creatively in any environment. I value creating designs backed by research that is true to the user, and active listening creates the best data for my work as a UX researcher. My ability to connect to these insights informs my design process as I create products that truly connect with what users need.

### **SKILLS**

User Experience Design | User Interface Design | HTML | CSS | Information Architecture | Heuristic Evaluation Competitive Analysis | Site Mapping | User Flow | User Research | User Interviews | Journey Map | Card Sorting | Tree Testing | Affinity Mapping | Research Synthesis | Persona | Sketching | Wireframing | Prototyping Usability Testing | Research Report | Spec Doc | Storytelling | Scrum | Agile | Presenting

### **SOFTWARE TOOLS**

PC/ Mac/ Linux | Google Suite/ Microsoft | Visual Studio | Sketch | InVision | Figma | Keynote | Zeplin | Trello

### **EXPERIENCE**

# UX Consultant — NY Adventure Club

New York, NY

Feb 2020 - Mar 2020

- Conducted comprehensive user research in order to improve the site navigation
- Revised the Information Architecture based on usability test results of the existing website, closed & open card sorting and tree testing results
- Used prototyping to test the revised navigation with users
- Compiled a specifications document as well as a research report
- Presented deliverables and usability testing results of Hi-Fi Mockup to stakeholders

# UX Design Fellow — General Assembly

New York, NY

Dec 2020 - Mar 2020

Designed responsive, user-centric products for web and iOS

- Collected and analyzed user behavior data through a variety of channels, such as user testing, semi-formal interviews, observation, surveys
- Worked cross-functionally with Engineering to incorporate user-centered research at all stages of the product cycle
- Studied and analyzed the user experience on multiples sites through a wide variety of qualitative methods
- Effectively communicated results and presented project deliverables

# QA Engineer — uTest

- Conducted projects as a freelance manual tester remotely
- Create detailed and well-structured test plans and test cases
- Reported bugs and created bug reports
- Communicated with the customer to clarify business requirements

New York, NY Nov 2018 - Nov 2019

### **EDUCATION**

General Assembly, NYC

Certificate in UX Design

Minsk State Linguistic University, Belarus

BA in Linguistics, Translation and Interpreting

### Université de Bordeaux

BA in Political Science and European Union Law

## **LANGUAGES**

English
Russian
Belarusian
French
German